欢迎来到新伦敦
我们有三条规则
没有隐私
没有家庭
没有一夫一妻制
所有人都很开心
美丽新世界
第一季 第一集
列宁娜·克朗
Lenina Crowne.
好吧
Fine.
你可真幸运
Well, aren't you a lucky girl?
谢谢
Thank you.
早上好
Good morning.
马克斯先生
Mr. Marx.
克朗小姐  谢谢你来
Ms. Crowne. Thank you for coming.
看来是急事咯
I guess it couldn't wait?
恐怕是的  请
I'm afraid not. Please.
黄色  看来很严重
Yellow? Sounds serious.
不非得的
Well, it doesn't need to be.
我的情绪水平没问题  谢谢
My levels are fine, thank you.
我注意到
It's come to my attention
你进入了一段专一的性关系
that you are engaged in an exclusive sexual relationship...
你说什么...等等
I beg your... hold on.
跟亨利·福斯特  他是一等+
With Henry Foster, an Alpha Plus,
已有两个月了
for over two months now.
不  并非如此  我不认为...
No, that's not accurate. I don't think...
这是上周
This is last week.
你记得吧
You do remember?
这是周一
This was a Monday.
高管厕所  在受孕区上方
Executive bathroom above the gestational wing.
等等  那不...
Wait, that's not...
两周前的周四  在有顶过道
Two Thursdays ago. The breezeway.
上周二  还是两次
Previous Tuesday. Twice.
-停下  -上周一  上上周一
- Stop. - The prior Monday. Monday before that.
好多个周一
Lots of Mondays.
请停下
Stop, please.
不  你不必感到羞耻
Oh, no. There's no need for shame.
列宁娜  我保证  这种事我早见怪不怪了
Lenina, I assure you I'm quite used to this sort of thing.
这是工作带来的影响
It comes with the job.
我能理解这种冲动
Well, I understand the impulse.
他帅气  魁梧  高大
He's handsome, strapping, tall.
是的  亨利·福斯特是个名副其实的一等+  是吧
Yes. Our Henry Foster is every bit the Alpha Plus, isn't he?
但我想不通的是
What I can never seem to wrap my head around, though,
这其中的自私
is the... selfishness.
两个人进行占有欲这么强  这么一对一
I mean, two people engaged in possessive, monogamous...
请原谅  我不知道还能怎么说
Forgive me, I don't know what else to call it...
私下  单独的交往
Relations in private, separate,
毫不考虑社会群体
with no regard for the social body,
毫不考虑他们造成的痛苦
no consideration for the pain they cause,
-他们造成的伤害  -不
- the damage they inflict... - No.
-抱歉  你说"不"吗  -就那几次
- Sorry, did you say "no"? - It was a few times.
-是22次  -就那么发生了
- 22. - It just happened.
你可以理解吧
You can understand that, can't you?
纯粹是性而已
It was purely sexual.
-打住吧  -我们先是聊了起来
- I'm gonna stop you right there. - First we began to talk,
我们喜欢彼此的陪伴
to prefer each other's company,
我就想...
and I just thought that that was...
不是的
No, you didn't.
你没想
You did not think.
你完全没有考虑你自己以外的人
You gave no thought whatsoever to anyone but yourself.
你没考虑你的同事  朋友
Not your colleagues, not your friends...
他们全都与你一样有权与亨利·福斯特享乐
All of whom have just as much a right to Henry Foster as you do.
难道你不这么想吗
Or do you not agree with that?
列宁娜
Lenina?
所有人都属于其他所有人
Everyone belongs to everyone else.
没错
Yes. That's right.
很好  很好
Good. That's... good.
这都结束了
Well, that's over now.
我发现  这种事
And I've found, with things like this,
最好就是回归本原
it's best to get right back in the mix,
专注于职责
to focus on one's duty.
如果你需要  我可以推荐几个好...
And if you like, I can recommend a few excellent, um...
请吧
Go on.
嗦麻吞一颗  苦难远离我
A soma a day keeps the jimjams away.
你不会有更...
You wouldn't happen to have something more...
要橘的吗
An orange for you?
这真的不怪你  列宁娜
This really isn't your fault, Lenina.
你是二等
You're a Beta.
亨利·福斯特是一等
Henry Foster's the Alpha here...
是二等+
Beta Plus.
-我是二等+  -当然
- I'm a Beta Plus. - Yeah, no. Of course.
我只是说  你本就不会想的那么超前
All I mean is that you can't be expected to think so far ahead.
而亨利需要考虑全局
Henry needed to consider the bigger picture.
而亨利
And Henry...
他没做到
Well, Henry didn't.
他也没考虑那些可能渴望你的人
Nor did he consider all of those who might desire you.
至少在今天之前没有
At least not until today.
亨利  跟你说的吗
Henry... Henry told you?
这不重要
It's not important.
重要的是我们及时发现了
What's important is that we caught it in time.
这种事一般会
These things have a habit of...
引发嫉妒
festering jealousy,
占有欲  秘密
possessiveness, secrecy.
列宁娜  你要采取建议行动
Lenina, you're going to take the recommended actions
你会好起来的
and you are gonna feel better.
我保证
I promise.
伯纳德·马克斯
Bernard Marx?
Bernard Marx.
你要无视我吗  马克斯
Are you ignoring me, Marx?
不  先生  绝不会
No, sir. I would never.
听着
Listen...
发生了一起事故
there's been an incident.
你去哪了
Where'd you get off to?
或者我该说"你去跟谁爽了"
Or should I say, "Who'd you get off with?"
芙兰妮  乖乖的
Frannie, behave yourself.
如果你说又是亨利·福斯特
If you say Henry Foster again,
我就要举报你
I swear I'll report you.
别傻了
Don't be silly.
扔掉好过修修补补
Ending is better than mending.
你是一个完美社会群体必不可少的一部分
You are an essential part of a perfect, social body...
所有人各司其职
Everybody in their place,
所有人现在都很快乐
everybody happy now.
英卓将我们紧密相连
And Indra keeps us all connected.
但想象一个世界  没有英卓的稳定与和谐
But imagine a world without Indra's stability and harmony...
一个充满贪婪
A primitive land of greed,
贪婪
迷信
superstition,
痛苦的原始之地
and pain.
痛苦
你不用想象
You don't have to imagine.
从新伦敦搭乘火箭仅需11分钟
Only an 11-minute rocket from New London,
蛮荒之地冒险乐园
即可抵达蛮荒之地
you'll find the Savage Lands.
渴望屋
来这里感受魔法吧
Come and experience the magic.
魔法
你带上朋友
You bring the friends;
朋友
我们提供欢乐
we've got the fun,
欢乐
由真正野人演出的写实节目每日上演
with realistic shows performed daily by actual savages.
专情屋
不幸
既能体验旧世界的所有不幸
All the misery of the old world
卓越体验酒店
又能享受在家般的舒适
with all the comforts of home.
舒适
蛮荒之地等你来冒险
Adventures await in the Savage Lands.
蛮荒之地冒险乐园
要热毛巾或嗦麻气泡水吗
Hot towel or soma fizz?
-要热毛巾或嗦麻气泡水吗  -谢谢
- Hot towel or soma fizz? - Thank you.
即将到达崇高区
Now arriving. District of the Sublime.
要热毛巾或嗦麻气泡水吗
Hot towel? Soma fizz?
你就是那个三等人吗  我是局里派来的
Are you the Gamma? I'm from the bureau.
顾问
Counselor.
-很高兴你能来  -嗯
- I'm happy you're here. - Yes.
发生什么了
What, uh... what happened?
我们的区民之前在进行娱乐活动
Our residents were enjoying a recreation session.
满足水平本来很高
Satisfaction levels were quite high
直到其中一个五等人  他...
until one of the Epsilons, he...
他出了事故
He had an accident.
真罕见
How rare.
带我去看看吧
Show me?
事故的确时有发生
They do happen, you know. Accidents.
-我就亲眼见过一次  -是
- I've seen one myself. - Yes.
但这起事故看起来...
But it seems that this accident was...
看你能不能弄明白吧
Well, see if you can make sense of it.
这边请  顾问
This way, Counselor.
让一下
Excuse me.
麻烦让一下  先生  谢谢
Excuse me, sir. Thank you.
你们几个杰克
Hey, you Jacks.
都让开
Get away from there.
杰克  听见我说的话了吗
Hey, you Jack. Did you hear what I said?
给你一颗嗦麻  杰克
A soma for you, Jack.
没什么好担心的  要嗦麻吗
Nothing to worry about. Soma?
给你一颗  来
One for you. Here you go.
今天天气很好  何必待在这浪费了
It's a fine day. Why waste it here, all right?
让这一带的区民离开
Clear the residents from the area, yeah?
我回来之前  叫这些五等人什么都别碰
And tell these Epsilons not to touch anything till I get back.
你要走了吗
You're leaving?
-你叫什么  -C杰克60
- What's your name? - CJack60.
你认识这个工人吗
You knew this worker?
我们认识这个工人
We knew this worker.
你看见他出了什么事吗
You see what happened to him?
回答我
I asked you a question.
这个工人坠楼了
This worker fell.
坠楼
Fell?
我们现在清理
We clean up now.
感受这份刺激
潜入
新感官世界
欢愉炸弹138
我记录感情  然后把它们转变为体验
I record feelings and turn them into experiences...
更广大  更大胆
Bigger, bolder,
海姆·沃森  感情制造师
超出你们的想象
better than anyone could imagine,
然后再交给你们  我亲爱的观众们
and I give them to you, my adoring audience.
不客气
And you're welcome.
我看着他的尸骸
I was just looking at what was left of him, and...
试着想象...
I tried to imagine what it...
那是什么感觉  爬上去
What it must have been like to... to... to climb up
从围栏上往下看  打算跳下去
and look over the edge and to plan it.
-做出这个选择  -我没听懂
- I mean, to choose it. - You lost me.
-选择什么  -自行了断  自杀
- Choose what? - To end himself, to die.
我不明白
I don't understand.
-因为他跳楼了  -跳楼
- 'Cause he jumped. - Jumped?
你的话说不通
You make no sense.
他为什么要跳楼  从没有人这么做过
Why would he? No one's ever done that.
-如果他当时很痛苦...  -他可以吃一颗嗦麻
- If he was in pain, if... - He could take a soma.
-万一嗦麻没用呢  -可是明明就有用
- What if soma didn't work? - But it does.
如果我说有一种痛苦
What if I said that there's a kind of pain
是嗦麻抑制不了的呢
that... that... that soma doesn't touch?
我会叫你吃一颗嗦麻
I'd tell you to take a soma.
这并不好笑
It's not funny.
我感觉到了他当时的感受
I felt it... what he felt.
-我碰了他  然后...  -一个五等人吗
- I... I... I touched him, and... - An Epsilon?
他一定有某部分
There must have been some part of him
-仍然和网络相连  -伯纳德
- that was still connected to the network... - Bernard.
和英卓以及所有人相连  和我
To Indra, to everyone... I mean, to me...
-那个五等人吗  -是的
- The Epsilon? - Yes.
你到底有没有认真听
Are you listening?
我都不确定五等人是不是真有感情
Not even sure they have feelings, the Epsilons.
别那么看我  你懂我的意思
Don't do that. You know what I mean.
我是指...
I mean...
像我们一样的感情
feel like we do.
他们和我们一样产生感情
They feel the same.
-你不太好  -我没事
- You're not well. - I'm fine.
我只是想解释一些事给你听
I'm just... I'm trying to explain something to you,
重要的事
something important.
我在听  我总是认真聆听  不是吗
And I am listening. I always listen, don't I?
因为我是你的朋友  伯纳德
'Cause I'm your friend, Bernard.
作为你的朋友  这话我只说一遍
And as your friend, I'm going to tell you this one time only.
你描述的这些感情
These feelings you described,
五等人并不具备
these aren't Epsilon feelings.
这是伯纳德才会有的感情
These are Bernard feelings.
不是你说的这样
No, this is not anything like that.
拜托  你有多少次坐在那张椅子上
Please. How many times have you sat in that very chair
-抱怨些什么...  -这次不同
- and then complained about... - This is different.
"在孵化场没人尊重我"
"No one respects me at the Hatchery."
"我觉得自己不是个一等＋"
"I don't feel like an Alpha Plus."
-别说了  -"我完全不知道要如何与人交流
- Stop it. - "I never know what to say to people.
我是伯纳德"
I'm Bernard."
我跟你说  我联接了他的...
I'm telling you that I connected with...
我产生了幻象
I had a vision.
不  你只是过了一个糟糕的下午
No, you had a bad afternoon.
你说你当时没有嗦麻了  是吗
You said you had no soma, right?
我用完了  因为全都分给了...
I ran... I ran out 'cause I had to give it all to...
那不就是了
Right. So there you have it.
你太过紧张了  就这么简单
You were overtaxed. Simple as that.
-这个五等人坠楼  让你...  -跳楼
- This Epsilon fell. Upsetting... - He jumped.
打住  我不想再听了
Stop it! I don't want to hear it.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我正在安排你今晚
I'm arranging for you to have my table
去我在享乐园的专座
at the Pleasure Garden tonight.
你为什么要...别这样
Why would you do... Please don't...
你要去那里认识一群年轻饥渴的人儿
You will go there, you will meet some young, eager thing,
做一些像你这样身居高位的人该做的事
and you will do what is expected of a man in your position.
你想和人建立联系  伯尼
You want to make a connection, Bernie?
那就在那儿做
Well, make it there.
因为老实说  朋友
'Cause quite frankly, my friend,
你要是不幸福  你就一无是处
if you're not happy, you're nothing at all.
这才对嘛
That's the spirit.
勾引人可不太好
It's not nice to tease.
谁规定的
Says who?
还有谁说我在勾引人了
And who says I'm teasing?
说好的"午夜前拒绝自降身份"呢
What happened to "never go minus before midnight"?
我只是在测试我的调戏范围
I'm just... testing the range of my "come hither."
算你运气好  你今晚不需要这么做
Well, lucky you. You won't need it tonight.
我真走运
Lucky me.
我打算这样
So here's what I'm thinking.
准备好了吗  说实话哦
You ready? Be honest.
不行吗  好吧
No? Okay. Fine.
反正这身有太多回忆了
Too many memories anyway.
这简直...
Wow, that is...
怎么  不是他的菜吗
What? Not his thing?
谁的菜都不是
It's not anyone's thing.
你又说不准
You never know.
去你的  是个人都喜欢性感小野猫
Fuck you. Everybody likes Sexy Cat.
你说是就是吧
If you say so.
你还是做自己吧
Maybe just be yourself.
你好  亨利
Hi, Henry.
这是芙兰妮
This is Frannie.
这是达蒙
This is Damon.
蛮荒之地
麦迪森
Madysun.
怎么
What?
我...
I just...
谢谢大家  谢谢...
Thank you, everyone. Thanks...
-你还好吗  -我看着像还好吗
- You okay? - Do I look okay?
当然不好  穿这一身热死了
Hell no. I'm hot as balls in this thing.
我天  约翰  你就不打算帮下我吗
Jesus, John, you gonna give me a fucking hand here, or what?
什么事
So?
天啊  有话直说
Christ, man. Spit it out.
-他们马上要来了  -不不不
- They'll be coming soon. - No, no, no.
你昨晚没来
You didn't show last night,
我以为发生了什么事
so I thought maybe something happened.
-没别的  -是这样
- It's not a big deal. - Right.
我昨晚去参加集会了
Yeah, there was a meeting last night.
-和你的团体吗  -嗯
- With your group? - Yeah.
你有时间一定要来一次
You gotta come sometime.
好可惜啊  我以为你会来的
It's too bad, you know? I thought you were coming over.
我想带你看看景色
I wanted to show you the view.
你已经给我看过了
You already showed me the view.
我想再带你看一次
I wanted to show you again.
-你真坏  -是吗
- You're bad. - Am I?
我跟你说过这不是个好主意
I already told you it's not a good idea.
为什么
Why not?
因为我和别人在一起了  傻子
Because I'm with somebody, dummy.
我知道  但我会对你好的
Yeah, but I'd be good to you.
那又有什么用
And what's that got to do with anything?
王八蛋
Dickhead.
懂我了吧
See what I meant?
-臭傻逼  -我真不想处理这种破事
- Fucking asshole. - I don't need to be dealing with this shit.
我在跟你说话呢  场工
I'm talking to you, stagehand.
你快走吧  我让他消消气
You better go. I'll cool him out.
今天的演出简直一团糟
Today's show was a fucking mess!
快走吧  约翰
Get the hell out of here, John.
亲爱的  跟我来
Baby, come with me.
你让我们像一群傻子似的出尽洋相
You made us look like a bunch of fucking idiots out there.
我拿这破玩意怎么演
How am I supposed to work with this shit?
-抱歉  克维尔  -去你的道歉
- Sorry, Kvle. - Fuck your sorry, man.
你的问题就是根本不在乎
You don't care. That's your problem.
我不懂
I don't understand
你就不能拿出专业的态度来对待哪怕一场演出
why you can't just be professional for one goddamn show...
我们说过  演出时使用武器
As we discussed, you have to check the firing pin
你就得提前检查撞针
before you use a weapon in the show...
该检查撞针的是你  道具仔
You check the fucking firing pin, prop boy.
干好你的活
Do your job!
记清楚了
And get it through your head...
我们要是没演好
We don't do it right,
游客可能就不会来了
then maybe they stop coming.
游客要是不来  我们就没饭吃
And if they stop coming, we don't eat.
你不会还要让我等你吧
I know you're not gonna make me wait for you.
混蛋
Jerk-off.
这下开心了吗
You had enough yet?
道具组
蛮荒之地冒险乐园
游客止步
把山羊给我就行
Just give me the goat.
是这样  朋友  我看重质量
Look, friend, I deal in quality.
这是完整的一套
It's a complete set.
我不能就这么把它拆了
I can't go breaking it up
就因为你这种  偏好
just 'cause you got certain... preferences.
把山羊给我
Just give me the goat.
这次你要买点什么吗
You're gonna buy something this time?
好东西都在哪
What happened to the good stuff?
你在说什么  我这全是好东西
What are you talking about? All I got is good stuff.
"迈伦·豪萨和大惨败"
"Myron Hauska and the Fiascos"?
这是"米米的单身组合"
This is "Mimi's Bachelorette Mix."
米米  超前于时代
Mimi... ahead of her time.
"一起认识图形"  哥们  这很烂
"Let's Learn Shapes"? This is bullshit, man.
我还在做生意
I'm trying to conduct some business here.
把山羊给我
Give me the goat.
这些是很稀有的图腾艺术品
These are rare totemic artifacts.
我在地下两米多挖到了它们
I found them eight feet down,
上面还沾着些死了的恶心玩意儿
some dead son of a bitch still clinging.
好的  你找到了心头好
All right. You found your jam.
你这儿有史以来最好的货
Best thing you got in here. Like, ever.
怎么  你不喜欢吗
What? You don't like it?
这是音乐  兄弟
It's music, man.
没人再写新歌了
They ain't making anymore of it.
她有约会对象吗
She seeing anybody?
什么东西
What's that?
拿着
Take it.
-告诉她我很抱歉  -离她远点
- Tell her I'm sorry... - Just stay away from her.
好  我做不到这点
Yeah. I can't do that.
我不
I don't...
我来帮你
I'm gonna help you out.
你听的这东西
You know, the stuff you listen to
说什么找到个姑娘
about finding the girl
然后开车向夕阳驶去
and driving off into the sunset
听起来不错  但是
sounds nice, but...
这没那么容易
it ain't that easy.
对男人来说最危险的就是成为一个浪漫的人
Most dangerous thing a man could be is a romantic.
这是谁
Who is this?
没人知道
No one knows.
妈  你在干嘛
Mom, what are you doing?
约翰  你好
John. Hello.
你今天出门了吗
Did you go outside today?
对  我是说
Yeah, I mean...
我  我努力了  真的
I... I tried. I did.
我真的努力  但是那个可怕的女人就在那
I really tried, but that horrible woman was out there
和那些坏小孩一起
with those vile children.
她对我面露凶色  约翰
She gives me nasty looks, John,
就好像她想用手杖狠狠打我
like she wants to club me with that cane of hers.
你想生气就生
If you're gonna be mad, be mad,
但别什么话都不说
but please don't get quiet.
你知道我没法忍受你什么话都不跟我说
You know that I can't stand it when you won't speak to me.
天啊
Oh, my God.
有什么问题
What's wrong?
问题在于你在窗户前这么坐着
What's wrong is that you're sitting here in front of the window
让所有邻居都看到  好像你是...
for the whole neighborhood to see you like you're...
继续  说啊
Go on. Say it.
继续
Go on.
再穿点衣服
Put some clothes on.
悠着点  不然之后没得喝了
Go easy. That's gotta last.
真好吃
It's really good.
光线合适时  你看起来真像他
In certain light, you look exactly like him.
如果我再稍微闭上眼睛
If I were to close my eyes a little,
就好像  真惊人
it's as if... remarkable...
-妈  -怎么了
- Mom. - Yeah?
不  你应该知道
No, I mean, you should know this...
-不  -是  这是你的身份
- No. - Yes, it's who you are...
请别说了
Please stop.
约翰
John.
麦迪森
Madysun?
你痛苦吗
Are you in pain?
痛苦
Pain?
不  你能不能帮我的手腕松绑
No. I mean, maybe you could untie my wrists.
你是谁  麦迪森在哪里
Who are you? Where's Madysun?
麦迪森  麦迪森
Madysun? Madysun!
她在哪
Where is she?
跟我来
Come with me.
我想给你看些东西
I wanna show you something.
约翰  在这  往那边看
John, up here. Stay with me.
你知道那是什么吗
You know what that is?
我在那工作
I work there.
那是一种亵渎
What you see there is an obscenity.
那些外人来到这里  占领我们的土地
These outsiders come here, take our land.
他们为了自己的欢愉修建了那羞辱
They build that insult for their own amusement.
我不想被嘲笑
I don't like being laughed at.
你想吗
Do you?
不想
No.
那你为什么放任他们
So why'd you let them?
麦迪森  麦迪森
Madysun? Madysun.
她没法帮你
She can't help you.
我觉得你犯了个错误
I think you made a mistake.
我觉得你抓错了人
I think you have the wrong person.
麦迪森
Madysun!
我们需要你  约翰
We need you, John.
我看着你
I watch you...
每天
every day...
清洗那些车
washing those cars.
为这些外人表演
Putting on plays for these outsiders,
这些新世界的人
these New Worlders.
他们什么都不热爱  什么都不信仰
They love nothing. They believe in nothing.
看那边的蓝色恐怖
Look at that blue horror out there.
我们哪怕碰到一点都会被烧成灰烬
Burns you and me to ash if we so much as touch it,
然而  他们却径直穿过
and yet, they walk right through.
他们是怎么做到的
How do they do that?
甚至让你怀疑他们是否是人
Makes you wonder if they're even human.
-你想知道那里有什么吗  -不
- You wanna know what's in there? - No.
-你的命运  -不  不
- Your destiny. - No, no.
不  等下
No! Wait!
不  不
No, no.
等下
Wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
生死全靠你的智慧和你的意愿
A chance to live or die by your own wits, your own will.
睁开你的双眼
Open your eyes.
我们要把它全部摧毁  约翰
We're going to tear it all down, John,
夺回属于我们的东西
take back what's ours.
你想让我做什么
What do you want me to do?
问题错了  宝贝
You're asking the wrong question, sweetheart.
你应该问问自己  我是谁
The question you gotta ask yourself is "What am I?"
一个自由的人
A free human being?
还是洗车机器
Or a washer of cars?
C杰克67
马克斯  你在做什么
Marx, what are you doing?
你为什么不在线
Why are you off-line?
我没有  我只是离开了一小会  我
I wasn't. I mean, for a moment, sir, I'm...
你都会做些什么
What is it you do?
做什么  长官
"Do," sir?
在独处的时候
When you're alone.
我看了你的动向
I reviewed your activity.
你最近很独来独往啊
You've been private lately.
-不  我没有吧  -你有
- No... have I... have I? - Yes.
取下镜片  关闭网络  断联
Optic out, off network, disconnected.
最近没有性行为  没有参加集体活动
No recent sexual connections, no communal...
我只是自行支配我的空闲时间
Well, that's just a matter of free time...
这是不可接受的  伯纳德
That's unacceptable, Bernard.
这是唯我主义
It's solipsism.
恶心之至
It's disgusting.
隐私是社会群体决不能容忍的恶习
Privacy is a vice the social body simply can't afford.
一等不需要别人来告诉他这些
I shouldn't need to explain this to an Alpha.
这么说  你可并不完全是一等
But then, you're not quite an Alpha,
你是吗
are you?
我是一等+  长官
I'm an Alpha Plus, sir.
收拾干净
Clean yourself.
解释一下这个
Explain this.
这只是个西柚
It's a grapefruit.
是你在今天事故现场扔下去的那个西柚
It's the grapefruit you dropped at the incident today.
为什么要这样做
Why would you do such a thing?
你去那里是为了评估每个人的情感创伤
You are to assess emotional trauma
分给他们嗦麻
and administer soma accordingly.
那个五等人
The Epsilon...
我只是想
I wanted...
理解他
to understand.
他坠楼了  你知道吧
You understand he fell?
如果你觉得不是坠楼  就很荒谬
To believe otherwise would be irrational.
对不对
Isn't that right?
说实话  伯纳德  你看起来状态不对
To be honest, Bernard, you don't look well.
我  我很好  长官
I'm... I'm fine, sir.
你可一点也不好
Not well at all.
你已经精疲力尽了
Depleted, exhausted.
来度个假如何
Have you considered a vacation?
不允许拒绝
It isn't up for debate.
我知道个地方  对你来说正好
I know just the thing to sort you out.
欢迎来到蛮荒之地
Welcome to the Savage Lands!
请我进去吗
You gonna invite me in?
你不是想带我看看吗
I thought you wanted to show me the view.
今晚不行
Not tonight.
别这样嘛
Don't be like that.
你到底想要我怎样
How the... do you want me to be?
你应该感恩
Grateful.
我们给了你一个机会
We're giving you a chance.
你的要求我做不到
I can't do what you're asking.
不是我
It's not me.
我喜欢你  约翰  但其他人...
I like you, John, but the others...
答应我  考虑一下吧
Promise me you'll think about it.
我可真不希望你出事
I'd hate for anything to happen to you...
或是你妈出事
Or your mom.
列宁娜  你怎么...
Lenina, what are you doing...
我试过你说的一切
I did everything you said.
我重新连接了  我服了嗦麻  抚摸别人  给予
I reconnected... I took, I touched, I gave.
这不符合你的阶级
This is inappropriate at your level.
我的阶级  那你呢
At my level? What about you?
我  我告诉你
Me? I'll have you know...
我今晚看见你了
I saw you tonight,
独自一人站在那里
standing there alone,
还像个懦夫一样逃跑了
running away like a coward.
真是个伪君子
You're a hypocrite.
-你在听我说话吗  伯纳德  -我在听
- Did you hear me, Bernard? - Yes.
我并没有感觉更好
I don't feel better.
我也是
Neither do I.
你说什么
What did you say?
我累了
I'm tired.
看起来我陷入了某些麻烦
And it seems that I'm in some sort of trouble.
长官说我最近独来独往
I've been told my behavior is private.
我经常不在线
I've been off network.
但我知道我应该怎样做
But I know what's expected of me,
所以我才  去尝试
so I... I try to...
性对我不成问题
I don't have a problem with sex. I don't.
性对我而言是
I mean, sex is something that I...
相信我  性对我而言
Believe me, sex is something that I... I...
这不是真实的
It's not real.
什么不是真实的
What's not?
这一切
Any of it.
我说不上来  这一切
I don't know. It.
还有我
Me.
我不是我应当成为的样子
I'm not who I'm supposed to be.
每个人都知道
Everyone sees.
说不定我能帮帮你
Maybe I can help with that.
英卓看不出区别吗
Can't Indra tell the difference?
这能骗过它吗
I mean, does this work?
投影我们自己
Projecting ourselves?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我一直想试试
I've always wanted to try.
对于亨利那件事
You were wrong,
你想错了
about Henry, I mean.
吸引我的不是因为他是一等+
It wasn't the Alpha Plus of him that pulled me in.
那是什么
What was it?
也许是我的条件训练
Maybe it's my conditioning.
我可是个优秀的科学家
I'm a good scientist.
我总是很好奇  总想看到更深层的东西
I've always been curious, wanted a look inside things.
亨利允许我看他的内心
Henry let me.
那你能看到我的内心吗
Do you see inside me?
你看到了什么
What do you see?